UNITE Boston Joint Board Records 6000/056
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Correspondence (Box 12)
  - FR Shirt Negotiations, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Forecaster of Boston, 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Arthur Freedberg, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Griffin Manufacturing, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - C.F. Hathaway, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Hit or Miss (Avon), 1995-1997 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Ideal Bias Binding, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Collective Bargaining Extension for Nautica- Mailed 12/19/02, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Nautica Closing, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Warn Notice, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Nautica Negotiations, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Needle Trade Services, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Riverside Mfg. Meeting, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    2/20/96 10:00am
  - Riverside Negotiations, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Riverside Grievances, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Agreement- Gerber Operators- Riverside Incentive Rate, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    Nov. 1, 2000
  - CMA Agreement- Riverside Mfg., 2004 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - SACO Defense, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Shepard Clothing, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Southwick Correspondence, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Letter of Understanding Between Southwick and UNITE, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    4/29/99
  - Specialty Filaments, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - State Coat Front, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Sterlingwear, 2001-2004 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - US Health Care- Sterlingwear, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Swiss Art Grievances, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Swiss-Art, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Tartan Textile, 2000-2003 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Tartan Textiles Proposals, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Meeting with Debbie Flagg, Martie V., 1998 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    UUSC July 10, 1998 2:00pm
  - Unitarian Universalist Service Comm. UUSC- Correspondence, 1998-2002 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Westpoint, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Miscellaneous, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Contracts (Box 13)
  - A and L Pleating, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Alicare, 1998-2007 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - American London, 2001-2003 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - American London, 1995-2000 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Andover Shop, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Apparel America (Capital Swimwear), 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Apparel America (Capital Swimwear), 1994-1997 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Avon (Hit or Miss), 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Bay State Curtain, 1998-2003 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Biddeford Blankets, 2002-2005 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Bixby, 1996-2003 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Bradley Scott Clothes, 1998-2001 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Brooks Brothers, 2000-2006 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - CHF Industries, 1997-2006 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Camden Tanning Corporation, 1996-1999 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Churchill Linen Services, 1996-2004 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Liz Claiborne, 2003-2006 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Liz Claiborne, 2000-2003 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Liz Claiborne, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Crystal Manufacturing, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Dyecraftsmen, 2001-2004 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - ECI Sportswear, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Fall River Shirt, 1996-2006 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Fashion B Inc., 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Filene's, 2000-2004 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Arthur H. Freedberg Company, 1995-2004 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - General Dynamics Armament and Technical Products (SACO), 2005 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Good Luck Fashions, 1998-2000 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - C.F. Hathaway and Company, 1996-2001 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Waterville Shirt Co., 2001 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Hometex Design, 2002-2005 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Contracts (Box 14)
  - Ideal Bias Binding, 2002-2005 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Ideal Bias Binding, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Robby Len Warehouse Division, 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Lexcraft, 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Marv Sportswear, 1996-2005 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Madeira Twin Fashion, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Mass State Coat Front, 1996-2005 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Milton's Tailors, 1999-2005 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Joseph Mollica, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - National Envelope Company, 2000-2003 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - National Linen Services, 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - PICA, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Purity Services, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - RCM Manufacturing, 1997-2002 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Riverside Manufacturing, 1995-2007 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - SACO Defense, 1993-1996 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Shepard Clothing Company, 2002-2004 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Southeastern Massachusetts Home Health Aides, 1998-2004 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Southwick Clothing, 1999-2005 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Specialty Filaments, 2001-2005 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Specialty Filaments, 1996-2002 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Swiss-Art, 1997-2005 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Sterlingwear De Boston, 1996-2007 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    English and Spanish
  - Tartan Textiles, 2000-2003 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Unitarian Universities Services Committee, 1997-2003 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Van-Baalen Pacific, 1999-2002 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Wellhart Manufacturing, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - West Point Stevens, 2001-2004 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Yale Genton Clothes, 1996-2005 (Box 14, Folder 29)